hello Facebook no not Facebook you could
see who periscope we are not on Facebook
so as the title suggests hi smoked pot
la site for the first time in two weeks
the summaries in two weeks is always
would I go off of it for and my body was
screaming for it by the end of it so I'm
starting the next cycle so whenever I go
off of it for a period of time and then
smoking again
there's always epiphanies and ideas
waiting on the other end and it's a
return to source especially when I go
for a walk in nature one smoking it and
there is this video I keep meaning to
create and for some reason have not been
that how much of my disability and
healing journey for my body is tied into
the healing journey for the planet I
have a neurological immune disorder
there's a lot that fit under that
umbrella but basically what I need to do
to in order to be able to heal is to
train my nervous system that it is safe
and seek and promote happiness in my own
body which is oxytocin and dopamine
that's what happiness is in scientific
terms although I'm in a unique position
because they're not all of the pain in
my body falls under that umbrella I also
have other things that are they caused
pain then the pain loop starts and my
body reacts to fake pain like it's real
and it's a feedback loop which is I
think very similar to what our planet
and the people on it are doing we kind
of have a neurological immune disorder
on this planet and we're looking at the
symptoms the racism the homophobia the
disconnect the poverty the well and then
the actual physical conditions people
have and we're trying to treat the
symptoms instead of the underlining
condition what I say
a powerful step forward and what came
through last night was how important it
is for individuals to feel safe and
happy and that's actually something we
can offer one another right now and it
is something that is sorely lacking in
our society at the moment I don't know a
single person who feels safe I feel a
sense of safety that I have never had
access to before if he already is
I truly am happy and safe I my special
interest since very young age has been
figuring out what the atrocities of the
planet are both that we do to each other
that we do to the planet and I believe
that's a lot of where my disorder has
come from but I can't unlearn what I
know so in order to actually gain a
level of actual safety I have to save
the world that is in a nutshell Who I am
what I'm here to do and yet I would like
my body to be my nervous system to be
actually feeling safe or it's not
reacting like there are Tigers when it's
a sight sneller sound that's not Tiger
we're safe
you're okay you can go to non higher
alert but that still exists I'm still
Trey I'm figuring that piece out but I
have a level of safety in my person
because the universe has my back because
I have people in my life that won't
cancel me then I have a level of safety
that JK rowling doesn't have with her
billions of doors
millions turn billions turned into
Millions because she gave most of the
way we live in a very scary world right
now where anything you say can get you
cancelled and it's the opposite of what
we actually need I haven't heard a
single actual solution to racism to
homophobia to ableism people have their
own will if everyone just was me and did
my learning and came to the same
conclusions they wouldn't be I'm like
well let's see let's see if it works if
you have a way for people to be less
racist can you use that way to feel less
anger towards the racists
then it does if yes awesome let's get it
out Laurel if no it's not a solution
if you can't train your body to not feel
hatred when you see a racist how do you
expect someone who's racist to train
their body to not have those thoughts
and ideas and so the people when they
feel the opposite of safety have racist
ablest homophobic things come out of
them that's the symptom we're not
dealing with the underlining cause if we
can help people truly feel safe they act
in a better way if we allow people to
truly seek happiness they get the
happiness and safety they get to give
back everything that unleashes and these
are these are the thoughts that are
going through my head when I smoke pot
last night of ten thousand since I was
ten thousand a second my head what
happens when we get together and create
safety for ourselves and each other and
happiness for ourselves in each other
now I can't actually offer you happiness
but the closest thing that we can offer
each other is connection connection
brings both safety a sense of I can't
tell you how safe it feels to find
people to talk about how to save the
world and know that they won't cancel me
know that because I've shown up and
developed a relationship even if I said
something absolutely horrific they would
let me tell my side they would they
would not just oh we're never talking to
you again that I don't feel with my
social justice warrior love them to
death but like they just are cancelling
people left it right and I'm like do you
feel safe do you not feel like you can
be canceled in a moment's notice for one
little slight one little thing we are
all reacting to the world internally and
of getting on tangents as as I will that
although
my mind wants to go to here's a new
media here's a new tech pal at forum
here's a social media platform here's
how we how we design it I get how one
I'm not the person to do that and also
technology's never actually the solution
creating community creating thriving
groups of people to just ask I right
before I smoke pot I put this thing on
Facebook because the next Saturday I was
going to host a solution raising slash
idea cafe on education in the Lower
Mainland because I want a solution to
education for September because I don't
feel comfortable sending my kid back to
social Vista nice school and yet I don't
want her to be at home isolated on her
iPad all day like she has been for
months and so although that's something
that I do need right now to thrive I put
out a call and then I took it down
because as soon as I smoke pot went for
a walk I was like oh this is bigger than
an education system I actually what I
want to ask people isn't how do I solve
your education problem for your family
it's how do we help you how do we help
you and your family thrive how do we
help each other thrive right now and to
me that is is getting to a state of
safety and Happiness for the individual
and that's going to be different for
everyone especially right now under cope
at 19 some people are like I'm not gonna
feel safe unless everyone's wearing
masks other people are like I feel very
unsafe that people are wearing masks
because look at those sheep look at
those sheep wearing masks I feel like
I'm all in this alone against the
government there isn't going to be a
policy that makes everyone feel safe we
are going to keep seeing how other
people's lack of safety and other
people's lack of information that we
want them to come to the same
conclusions as us is going to keep
causing more and more chaos in our
bodies and in the world and the way to
undo it is the same way I feel my body
with safety and Happiness which again is
their connection so although I'm not
getting to the actual solution which is
something along the lines of thriving
community and it has not because it
still requires a platform it's like no
this too complex it's not what I meant
to do is start an agile solution that
I'm able to implement right now I have
this amazing group of people that I meet
with every Wednesday for two hours the
purpose was it to eat for two hours but
we always end up eating for two hours
and the amount of benefit I've gotten
from that group and the stuff that is
currently now coming out of that group
although I didn't really put them
together till this week in fact one of
the people in that group is literally
who introduced me to the system I'm
doing that helps you feel safe and I'm
happiness right because it's very hello
Brooklyn it's very similar to what I was
doing naturally but because I need to
reveal the whole world for my body to
heal it's like okay baby we can heal my
body with safety and happiness before
before I fix all of the entire planet
and don't put that on my on my shoulders
but it's easier said than done what I
feel I have access to a solution when we
can create communities of people that
can come together and offer each other
connection true connection this is my
group I'm talking about that I wouldn't
be canceled from they would let me show
up basically no matter what I said in
public I'm pretty sure I could test it
but there's a sense of safety that
exists there that other people don't
have access to because they live in an
influence or social media world you
can't be safe when you're an influencer
right if your money if your platform is
a group of people who don't know you of
course you can be cancelled real true
friends who know your heart and soul
don't cancel you right when JK Rowling
said what she said and people canceled
her like would you cancel your mother
for saying that would you cancel your
aunt for saying that or would you have a
conversation would you still love them
as a whole human being and allow them to
be imperfect that is not what we are
offering each other on social media of
course but it is something we
actually can offer each other because
it's something we are all craving so
creating a way whether that's this
Facebook or this YouTube channel this is
a YouTube channel for people watching it
on periscope as well to be able to meet
with a handful of people week after week
after week and establish that you start
to realize how amazing human beings are
they are kind they're intelligent they
are good one-on-one we are amazing in
small groups of people we are amazing
it's when we get our news from the media
and they can point to the stupid the
stupidity and they can point to there
isn't a thing that can happen on the
planet right now that isn't going to
outrage somebody just commented on
someone's Facebook which maybe I
shouldn't know if because they were
freaking out but they're tearing down a
plane couldn't statue I was like who
cares literally there are thousands of
things to care about over Abe Lincoln
statue does it make sense they're
tearing down Abe Lincoln statue
probably not it's not really in
alignment with what they're trying to
accomplish but who cares it's a statue
Abe Lincoln doesn't care he's like right
so they shouldn't be doing it like are
you gonna go and put yourself between
them and the statue because unless
you're that committed stop
caring like it's really not on you
you're not even in the same country as
them and yet I'm caring about him
carrying so that's why I'm like maybe I
should leave comments about me at all
the more we can look at our own actions
and connect ourselves to each other the
better off we are
like we truly don't need to worry about
what anyone else is doing and what the
rest of the world is doing if we can
offer people happiness and connection
sorry happiness and safety which comes
from connection because the thing about
social media influence is it is dopamine
it is simply an addictive hit it is it
is addictive so like you you want to get
more then you're making decisions to get
more influenced and then one thing goes
wrong and that influence goes away and
your whole identity goes away because
you're cancelled and even if you're not
an influencer even if you're not JK
Rowling the fact that she gets canceled
for having the same thoughts that you
might have
and makes you silences you makes you
feel less safe your family and fret even
if you are someone's mother and aunts
right you're like oh they cancel JK
really but it's their favorite author
they're probably gonna cancel me if I
say that oxytocin is the actual
happiness
hey Chyna oxytocin is what we feel when
we love someone not when people love us
so possibly I felt oxytocin in my body
thinking of JK Rowling and Harry Potter
because I do love the Harry Potter
series and I love her for making it she
feels zero oxytocin towards me she
doesn't know that I exist
she might feel dopamine towards the like
fan base but the fan base can cancel you
and so there's something about celebrity
status that gives the mass is oxytocin
if you truly love them but not the
person who and then we're trying to be
this person instead of the oxytocin all
you have to do to feel oxytocin in your
body it's fall in love with a human
being whether celebrity whether your kid
whether your sibling fall in love and
the more we love one another the less
chances we have of that killing each
other but definitely that but cancelling
each other we don't cancel people we
love we let them make mistakes we let
them be whole human beings and then we
definitely don't do that to em so
answers and celebrities they do one
thing wrong and they fall from grace
because we don't eat Thanksgiving dinner
with them you don't know their their
trauma and everything else we don't
really love them because they can fall
from grace but as an individual you can
truly start loving people and so being
able to bring people together in small
groups doing things like having
answering the 36 questions there was an
article in one I'm gonna say the New
York Times and if you're on that like a
decade ago on 36 questions to fall in
love 36 questions for a connection and
I've done this on a few first dates I
actually did it with men when I thought
I was
straight and then I did it with women
when I figured I was queer and they are
powerful and I want to do something
similar to that like slow dating but not
dating like that finding your you're
monogamous soulmate you are falling in
love with other humans because you then
feel oxytocin
this isn't about so much of our lives is
spent trying to get people to like us
when that's not where oxytocin comes
from people loving you doesn't give you
oxytocin not if it's not reciprocated
you have to feel love and I know this
because I have a kid who I know she
loves me but she also literally States
the opposite constantly and I'm like you
know what you can't touch the love I
have for you
does it matter you can hate me you could
abuse me you can do absolutely anything
I am gonna love you to death I am gonna
love you exactly as you are
in this moment and I'm gonna fail and
I'm gonna love me through that to that
level of oxytocin is not what I thought
I would get for parenting because
parenting is supposed to be they like
are in awe of you I was supposed to be
an influencer as a parent right like
telling her what to do and she'd be
obedient I got the opposite opposite of
that but when I did get was an honor was
a love that doesn't require any any
anything it doesn't require her to be
anything but who she is and I get that
love by giving it not by getting it and
so that same love I can get from every I
can have from any human being I interact
with because I fall in love with them as
a human being as a full human being and
I get the oxytocin I get the happiness
hopefully I get a pass a bit of that on
to thanks hopefully it helps them fall
in love with themselves but it isn't
about that
and so if we are meeting in small groups
falling in love with ourselves and each
other we get something that is a natural
tractor from day one my Omega group was
a natural attractor from day one even
though we didn't know it yet even though
it was like there's something here we
can feel there's something that brings
us together that we have in common
that we found each other and although I
can't offer that because I don't know
what other people's game B is offering
that around anything offering that
around the 32 questions or 36 questions
and so what's coming up that I can do is
is reestablish the idea cafe with the 36
questions so get together and we're
gonna we're gonna go through them and
see I know the first one is like who
would you who would you invite to dinner
right that are alive who would you like
to have as a dinner guest
maybe it's the top three dinner guests
those are the kind of questions that
like anyone can answer
they aren't reliant on your intellect
they don't really their reliance on are
you gonna show up and it doesn't like it
is a natural human reaction to want to
say the right thing to want to be liked
but when you start to realize that all
of the oxytocin all the actual happiness
in your body comes from liking the other
person comes from truly falling in love
with people then it isn't who cares how
you answer the question I want to know
how you answer the question I want to
know who do you want to bring to dinner
right when you truly are in that moment
and trying and getting to know someone
you can fall in love with them there's a
level of safety that we feel when we can
truly be see it is all any of us are
craving it's why influencer exists it's
why celebrity exists it's why parenting
probably exists and yet we can offer it
to one another in a very real way that
isn't tweeting and on Facebook where
clearly people can get cancelled there
behind a screen
we don't have oxytocin for them at best
we have dopamine hits they're giving us
and hits forgiving them and so there's
something that came out last night that
was like okay if we can get in these
small groups have micro solidarity just
ask what would help you thrive what I
asked my kid last night like what's your
perfect world I don't know if anyone's
ever done vision boards I have oh so
much less into them now but I still have
a vision of what I want in my life
I'm just less than attached it has to be
a certain way
I would love to live early with a group
of people that we can sing around a
campfire at night that they can do
activities with my kids I'm never gonna
want to do and I can hang out with their
kids and raise that my kids not gonna
want to hang out with me we can it like
I have a vision of what I do I'm not
actually working towards it I'm just
keeping it as a vision in my head that
my kid can have an education that she
thrives in she really enjoys he and
sparks joy she doesn't even know she's
it's like I don't want to do school
that's time I've heard you have a
perfect world I'm like exactly so if you
don't feel like here in school she wants
her old school back she didn't know what
she had she's like all the schools
should be my old school I'm like yes but
how about your school's just your old
school maybe we don't make a blank and
education system for everyone when we
can get together offer what would help
us thrive what is our Pinterest board
what is our vision board right does that
mean I'm gonna give it to you am i
handing you beachfront property I'm not
handing me no one's handing me a rural
community of people who see me and like
me but being together and talking about
the five questions Who am I what is my
purpose for my people I miss one what do
I need and what what am I ready to let
go of or if that's to Louie for people
answering the 36 questions
what do you who do you want to invite to
dinner I can't remember what the next
one is some of them are more deep like
like what is your relationship with your
mother like we can show up and have
actual conversations and leave a
conversation feeling loved and the more
we can make mistakes cuz we also have
social anxiety and so we like go over
what we said in our head afterwards but
the more you know you can keep coming
back and being invited back and the no
one else is is fixated on what you said
the more you realize your voice matters
your voice you can speak and they'll be
safe and we can offer that to one
another in a way that even if because
you're not an influencer you're not
gonna get a million fans and then be
canceled you're gonna have people that
you meet and fall in love and you're
like why would I meet with that person
more and the more likely
where to see them so I know I'm all over
the place we can offer each other weekly
conversations an actual group can get to
know really well and that's not safe for
some people
nor is it kind of an entry point so we
can also have a possibility of people to
explore who they are and be connected
with multiple people right so you show
up on Wednesday at 2 p.m. you happen to
be connected with these three people and
have a conversation then you start to
develop relationships and you start to
say hey I want to have a weekly one on
the Villa Wednesdays if for who else is
available Wednesdays at 4 are the people
I've met with before and then establish
more concrete groups who can have these
conversations like my mega group the
beauty of that although I want solution
raising
I want groups of people who want to get
together and talk about what we can
actually do with 10,000 people at
$100,000 that is one form of a group in
a small form of group and so people who
are answering the 36 questions people
are answering the five questions people
who whatever their version is right any
small group if you concentrated on
something that's gonna connect us
actually help us feel oxytocin actually
help us feel like we're safe then from
that space ideas will emerge problems
will also emerge right like ooh what you
need to thrive is food what I need to
thrive is better food that is something
we can offer as an idea that solution
raising can even if we're not in
solution right even if we don't want to
actually sit and talk about socials for
an hour there's enough of us that do but
there's definitely 10,000 people who
want to connect and be seen and loved
and will generate ideas and so having
something as simple as groups of people
coming together and asking what would
help you thrive who wants to answer the
36 questions who wants to answer the
five questions like how do we put you in
groups so that you are getting something
out of it from day one every
conversation you're part of is gonna
help you grow and gonna help you feel
connected and safe that doesn't mean you
get to feel connected and safe every
minute of every day
but you're gonna keep showing up and
realizing more and more the universe has
your back we got your back you get to be
you what
get out of that you then want to offer
the rest of the world and so it's a
natural attractor some of those people
are going to be like me and my people
who like having solution raises so as
ideas come up I'm like what we need is a
better education system what my family
needs is for me to literally who are the
other people who want to live in a rural
community that you know more cohousing
but rural that we can start to form
communities around our goals and our
missions and actually help each other
achieve it instead of the idea that I
need a Pinterest board and I need to go
make mega money so that I can make it
happen and the universe has my back
because I think positively and I'm
grateful for everything no because I can
tell you how many people have vision
boards and how many people actually
achieve what's on their vision board
next to zero and the few that do they
get their YouTube channels they know the
influence respect all of them but we can
actually help each other achieve our
dreams without it being a mandatory
thing again no one's had a new
beachfront property but if that's what
you're focused on day in and day out I
guarantee you at some point some will be
like ah you can come state mine for a
week like sure I'm not there for a week
you'd own the house it and you're either
going to figure out yes this is
something I want to be in and figure out
how to live towards that or it's not
gonna hold its charm
you'll be like actually kind of a go
though beachfront property I know I'm
I've been on for too long already was
only funded we don't feel like 10
minutes but I do want to do a video on
my disability what it's taught me
because it is exactly how we kill the
world yet my body saw heal me there's
the world like it's like I'm on the path
to safety and happiness I have a level
of safety that next to nobody I know has
I am poor I am sick and I cannot be
canceled not because I actually can't
because you're God I could be but
have connection that I actually would
have thought came from my family but my
family's actually cancelled me in a way
that made it safer like I was like oh
you're not gonna be the people who see
the beauty in me you're not going to be
the people who see my goals and help me
achieve them because you I'm not that
person to you me and my sister have a
little bit canceled each other premiere
our lives at the moment which is not
something I would've ever thought
possible
my aunt's cancelled me out of her life
because I remained friends with her ex
weight things that like to I insisted
finder like but wait I asked you if I
could and you said yes this makes no
sense whatsoever but family isn't the
safety net I thought it was but in so
losing that safety net I got a different
sense of safety like okay I have found
real community and connection that means
I can't be canceled because even if I am
I can find new I can find I don't know
if there's another game be out there but
the more I show up and the more I'm not
canceled for things that I say and do
the more I realize that this is safe for
me this is what I belong and because I
found it once if it does for some reason
fall apart I will create something or
find something else and I don't get that
because I'm better than other people I
get that because I've given it to myself
I've given myself a level of safety
that's like I'm not gonna cancel me I
love me I'm gonna keep showing up I go
for a walk in nature and nature has my
back I'm like oh thank you right if
nothing else I can return to mother
nature nobody else kids you can't cancel
that I mean you could I guess I could
get put in prison or something let me
take it away from nature but even then
I'll have it in my mind like there's not
something somebody else can do to me
besides actually kill me it's gonna take
away what is coming from inside this
sense of safety and happiness I go for a
walk and I look like a crazy person
because I am oute and sing to myself I
guarantee you other people by that
very awkward I'm like you don't
understand how hat like this reignites
my soul nothing you have can reignite my
soul so why would I give this up for
that and the more you show up in the
world and not act authentically yes you
were gonna trigger people who are not
acting authentically but you also give
people permission to do that more
themselves and so although I know I just
really explained because it never is
concrete but to be able to come together
and create thriving communities create
small groups of people who a way for
them to find each other a way for them
to find each other in one-off
conversations which is what the idea
Cafe was kind of trying to be but now I
don't even unit for to try and be
anything I'm like oh I already have this
in my life what would offer it to you
yeah you to Shila will talk to you
thanks for hanging out for a bit only
beyond like other minute or so that when
we and that's all it requires so that's
what I'm looking for is people who are
committed to safety and Happiness and
that means that has to be the highest
order above PC culture love like needing
to be right above median statues to be
torn down or not torn down or eating
people to wear masks or not wear masks
how do we help each other feel safe how
do we offer actual safety to know that
you will not starve your kids will not
starve no matter who or what you are
it's a level of safety we have never
felt on this planet and I can't offer
that from day one we can offer small
groups and when 10,000 people get
together we realize oh food I don't want
to know we're not gonna starve I want to
know my kid is gonna be loved and
accepted no matter what their race
gender sexuality is these things are
gonna come up and then we can actually
deal with them and put forward problems
do solution raisings on and once there's
an idea that's actually generated we can
have 10,000 people come on board and be
like yes I want that solution and then
it gets made but having a bigger
community of
well whose purpose is simply connection
simply safety and happiness and it
doesn't mean everything as part of being
safe there's knowing you get to up
and and still be welcome which means
we're all gonna up and we have to
figure out how to also still be welcome
it's just about doing it repeatedly very
few of us are gonna up on the grand
scale of what exists in council culture
because they can only exist in canceled
culture only exists when it goes viral
right if I say something shitty 20 if my
friends are gonna hear it if it's on my
Facebook page a million or not it's just
not my influence circle but anything
could go viral at any point and so we
have this like lack of safety this is
the point universe to me I'm still be
watching it so thanks for hanging out
those that did and safety and Happiness
so anyone who's committed to that please
like and subscribe to this channel
because we are going to create a sense
of safety and happiness for one another
and I know I can offer that because I
feel it 90% of the time I know I'm safe
I know the universe has my back I know
the people in my life have my back
how's the universe does they can't do
anything but help me even when they're
annoying me even when they're
frustrating me the universe has my back
and there's also a sense of safety a
true sense of safety that I'm not gonna
feel until I know that I'm fed and my
kids fed no matter what and I know we
can create that together much more
effectively than what we are doing which
is causing people to not feel safe and
happy like asking them to remove
happiness from their life just give up
your Starbucks just give up
JK Rowling give up everybody oh that
doesn't make me feel happy and it
doesn't make me feel safe and if we can
come together with those as our mission
then we can create safety and happiness
for everyone and then they show up
better and we get all the gifts they
release for that so I can subscribe and
I'll be back the next time the universe
tells me to let talk to the universe
that's that's how a lot better
scheduling